[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Director Bob Clark made a cameo in the film A Christmas Story.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the Aye-aye traditionally associated with according to ancient Malagasy legends?", "correct_answer": "Death", "incorrect_answers": ["Future marriage", "Rain", "Luck"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of topaz is the gemstone of Texas?", "correct_answer": "Blue topaz", "incorrect_answers": ["Imperial topaz", "Orange topaz", "Mystic topaz"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What causes the death of MI6 agent, Paula Kaplan, in the motion picture, Thunderball?", "correct_answer": "Cyanide capsule", "incorrect_answers": ["Radiation sickness", "Venomous snake", "Laser beam"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This became the longest running Broadway play on 9 January, 2006 .", "correct_answer": "Phantom of the Opera", "incorrect_answers": ["The Fantasticks", "Les Miserables", "Mouse Trap"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Are baby flamingos pink?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of Indian animals are included in the so-called Big Four selection?", "correct_answer": "Poisonous snakes", "incorrect_answers": ["Largest insects", "Most dangerous animals", "Largest land animals"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What other use does the Brazil nut oil have, apart from being used for food?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["In cosmetics", "In clocks as lubricant", "In making paint for artists"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the other common name of the shade of green known as midnight green?", "correct_answer": "Eagle green", "incorrect_answers": ["Hunter green", "Teal", "Feldgrau"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What did Skip say in the movie Dead Presidents when he was told his girlfriend was looking for him?", "correct_answer": "Im at where Im at, and I be where I be", "incorrect_answers": ["What for", "Tell her Im over here", "So?"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What human internal organ contains Luschkas crypts?", "correct_answer": "Gallbladder", "incorrect_answers": ["Uterus", "Urinary bladder", "Stomach"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Excavations and research prove that pi was known as early as 20th century BC, when ancient Babylonian mathematicians used what value value for it?", "correct_answer": "25/8", "incorrect_answers": ["104348/33215", "22/7", "3.12"]}]